John A. Lomax and Alan Lomax papers
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Correspondence, 1925-1952 and undated
  - Subseries V: Alan Lomax and Huddie "Lead Belly" Ledbetter, 1938-1941
    - 1938-1941 (Box-folder 8/254)
      - Alan Lomax to Huddie "Lead Belly" Ledbetter, 1941-11-06
      - Huddie "Lead Belly" Ledbetter to Alan Lomax, 1941-12-01
      - Huddie "Lead Belly" Ledbetter to Alan Lomax, 1942-03-10
- Series II: Fieldwork, 1933 and undated
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1933 (Box-folder 8/255)
  - New Orleans, Louisiana, 1933 (Box-folder 8/256)
  - Mexico, undated (Box-folder 8/257)
- Series III: Personal, undated
  - University transcripts (Box-folder 8/258)
  - Finance (Box-folder 8/259)
- Series IV: Professional Activities, 1934-1942 and undated
  - Subseries I: Archives Administration, 1934-1942 and undated
    - Annual Report to the Librarian of Congress (Box-folder 8/260)
    - Annual Report to the Librarian of Congress, 1934, 1937 (Box-folder 8/261)
    - Archive of American Folk-Song indexes, lists, logs, reports, transcripts, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 8/362)
    - Archive of American Folk-Song indexes, lists, logs, reports, transcripts (Box-folder 8/263)
    - Commercial recordings research documents including Robert Johnson recordings (Box-folder 8/264)
    - Library of Congress personnel documents, Alan Lomax (Box-folder 8/265)
    - List of Game Songs (Box-folder 8/266)
    - List of Hollers (Box-folder 8/267)
    - National Defense Program correspondence (Box-folder 8/268)
    - National Defense Program memoranda, 1941 (Box-folder 8/269)
    - National Defense Program manuscripts, 1941 (Box-folder 8/270)
    - National Defense Program song transcriptions, 1941 (Box-folder 9/271)
    - National Defense Program song transcriptions, Raider Battalion, 1941 (Box-folder 9/272)
    - National Defense Program, 1941 (Box-folder 9/273)
    - Notebook, 1941 (Box-folder 9/274)
    - Notes on recordings in the archive, undated (Box-folder 9/275)
    - United Federal Workers of America newsletters, pamphlets, lecture notes, undated (Box-folder 9/276)
  - Subseries II: Contacts, undated
    - Texas research documents (Box-folder 9/277)
    - U.S. South research documents, undated (Box-folder 9/278)
    - Research documents, undated (Box-folder 9/279)
    - John Lomax's address books, undated (Box-folder 9/280)
    - Address books, undated (Box-folder 9/281)
  - Subseries III: Grants, undated
    - ACLS grant application (Box-folder 9/282)
  - Subseries IV: Presentations, 1939-1942 and undated
    - Lecture notes (Box-folder 9/283)
    - "Ballads" (Box-folder 9/284)
    - "Dance Music" (Box-folder 9/285)
    - "Folklore Collecting," etc. (Box-folder 9/286)
    - "Of Men and Books" (Box-folder 9/287)
    - "Singing Country: European Heritage" (Box-folder 9/288)
    - "Spirituals" (Box-folder 9/289)
    - "Toward a Scientific Folklore" (Box-folder 9/290)
    - American Musicological Society (Box-folder 9/291)
    - CBS School of the Air Conference in Mexico City, 1939 (Box-folder 9/292)
    - Columbia Lecture Bureau, publicity, 1941 (Box-folder 9/293)
    - Council of the General Federation of Women's Clubs, circa 1940 (Box-folder 9/294)
    - Griffith Music Foundation Conference, circa 1940 (Box-folder 9/296)
    - Indiana University Folklore Institute, 1941 (Box-folder 9/297)
    - Progressive Educational Association, Washington, D.C., 1942 (Box-folder 9/298)
    - School Broadcast Conference, 1940 (Box-folder 9/299)
    - Texas Folk Songs, 1940 (Box-folder 9/300)
    - Washington, D.C. Librarians' Meeting (Box-folder 9/301)
    - Fisk University, 1938 (Box-folder 9/302)
    - The White House, program, 1941 (Box-folder 9/303)
    - The White House, press release, clippings, 1939 (Box-folder 9/304)
  - Subseries V: Publicity, 1939
    - Clippings about John A. Lomax (Box-folder 9/305)
    - Clippings about Alan Lomax (Box-folder 9/306)
- Series V: Sound Recording Projects, undated
  - Flyer for The Ballad Hunter (Box-folder 9/307)
  - Lecture notes and proposal for six albums (Box-folder 9/308)
- Series VI: Research Materials, 1911-1941 and undated
  - "A Question of Academic Freedom," Columbia University (Box-folder 9/309)
  - "For Sale Cheap," 1911 (Box-folder 9/310)
  - "Home on the Range" and "The Cowboy's Lament" song transcripts (Box-folder 9/311)
  - "In Abraham's Bosom" (Box-folder 9/312)
  - "Rural Community Planning," Works Progress Administration (Box-folder 9/313)
  - "An Opportunity to Help in an Important Work," Department of the Interior, 1937 (Box-folder 9/314)
  - Eva Westfelt, "The Great Titanic" song transcript (Box-folder 9/315)
  - Event flyers (Box-folder 9/316)
  - Federal Security Agency Publications (Box-folder 9/317)
  - Sheet music by Curley Fletcher, 1941 (Box-folder 9/318)
  - Edwin P. Lastrapes manuscripts on New Orleans (Box-folder 9/319)
  - Sheet music by Huddie Ledbetter for "Take a Whiff on Me" and "You Can Lose Me Charley" (Box-folder 9/320)
  - Lullabies (Box-folder 9/321)
  - Memphis Co. Workhouse song transcriptions (Box-folder 9/322)
  - Washington Political Cabaret (Box-folder 9/323)
  - National Recreation Association pamphlets (Box-folder 9/324)
  - Newspaper articles collected by Alan Lomax (Box-folder 10/325)
  - Recordings catalog of Jeffrey Fuller (Box-folder 10/326)
  - Clippings about Carl Sandburg (Box-folder 10/327)
  - Song transcripts (Box-folder 10/328)
  - Song transcripts (Box-folder 10/329)
  - Song transcripts (Box-folder 10/330)
  - Song transcripts (Box-folder 10/331)
  - Steinberg transcripts (Box-folder 10/332)
  - Research on Mrs. Daisy Tegtmeyer (Box-folder 10/333)
  - Texas Folklore Society meeting program (Box-folder 10/334)
  - Song transcripts by Ruby Lee Woods, 1940 (Box-folder 10/335)
- Series VII: Maps, 1933-1939 and undated
  - Arkansas, Colorado, Kansas, Mississippi, Missouri, New Mexico, Oklahoma, Texas (Box-folder 10/336)
  - Arkansas, Louisiana, Mississippi (Box-folder 10/337)
  - Canada (Box-folder 10/338)
  - Central America (Box-folder 10/339)
  - Delaware, Maryland, New Jersey, New York, Washington D.C. (Box-folder 10/340)
  - Florida (Box-folder 10/341)
  - Indiana (Box-folder 10/342)
  - Kentucky, Tennessee (Box-folder 10/343)
  - Maine (Box-folder 10/344)
  - Massachusetts, Rhode Island, Connecticut (Box-folder 10/345)
  - Michigan (Box-folder 10/346)
  - New Hampshire, Vermont (Box-folder 10/347)
  - New Jersey, Pennsylvania (Box-folder 10/348)
  - New York including a map of the 1939 New York World's Fair (Box-folder 10/349)
  - New York, 1939 (Box-folder 10/350)
  - Ohio (Box-folder 10/351)
  - Ohio (Box-folder 10/352)
  - Ohio (Box-folder 10/353)
  - Ohio (Box-folder 10/354)
  - Oklahoma, Texas (Box-folder 10/355)
  - Pennsylvania (Box-folder 10/356)
  - Pennsylvania (Box-folder 10/357)
  - South America (Box-folder 10/358)
  - Street guide to Washington, D.C. (Box-folder 10/359)
  - Virginia, West Virginia, Maryland, Delaware (Box-folder 10/360)
  - West Virginia (Box-folder 10/361)
  - Wisconsin (Box-folder 10/362)
  - Wisconsin (Box-folder 10/363)
  - Wisconsin (Box-folder 10/364)
  - Wisconsin (Box-folder 10/365)
  - Wisconsin (Box-folder 10/366)
  - Kentucky (Box-folder 10/367)
- Series VIII: Writings, 1907-1967
  - "14 Traditional Spanish Songs from Texas," forward (Box-folder 11/368)
  - "A History of the English Ballad Controversy," term paper by Alan Lomax, 1942 (Box-folder 11/369)
  - "About Abe Lincoln" (Box-folder 11/370)
  - "Coyote Wisdom," by John A. Lomax, Southwest Review (Box-folder 11/371)
  - "Home on the Range" correspondence and transcripts, 1938 (Box-folder 11/372)
  - "Home on the Range," mock radio script (Box-folder 11/373)
  - "How Buck Won His Freedom" tale (Box-folder 11/374)
  - "Moonshine Story" (Box-folder 11/375)
  - "Pray, But Don't Trust Too Much" (Box-folder 11/376)
  - "Raiford Florida Penitentiary" by John A. Lomax and transcripts of James "Iron Head" Baker tunes "Old Hannah" and "Love My Darlin'" (Box-folder 11/377)
  - "Rain or Shine" also known as "Doney Gal" (Box-folder 11/378)
  - "The Fruit of Yo Doin'" by Alan Lomax (Box-folder 11/379)
  - "The Vision of Eddie Wesley; A Tale of God's Doings" (Box-folder 11/380)
  - "Uncle John's Prophetic Error" (Box-folder 11/381)
  - Alan Lomax and Ruby P. Tartt (Box-folder 11/382)
  - Iron Head Baker by Alan Lomax (Box-folder 11/383)
  - Evanson-Harris-Lomax book, unpublished? (Box-folder 11/384)
  - Various manuscripts by John A. Lomax (1 of 2) (Box-folder 11/385)
  - Various manuscripts by John A. Lomax (2 of 2) (Box-folder 11/386)
  - W.T. Parks research documents (Box-folder 11/387)
  - Reverend R.R. Reese, "Knee Bent and Body Bowed" (Box-folder 11/388)
  - Review of "Mississippi Folk Songs" (Box-folder 11/389)
  - Smalls, Missy on Ben Smalls transcripts, 1938 (Box-folder 11/390)
  - Texas Folk Song (Box-folder 11/391)
  - Writings by John A. Lomax (Box-folder 11/392)
  - Writings and research documents (Box-folder 11/393)
  - Adventures of a Ballad Hunter by John A. Lomax (1947)
    - Preface (Box-folder 11/394)
    - Table of Contents (Box-folder 11/395)
    - Chapter 01: "Boyhood in Bosque" (Box-folder 11/396)
    - Chapter 02: "College" (Box-folder 11/397)
    - Chapter 03: "Hunting Cowboy Songs" (1 of 2) (Box-folder 11/398)
    - Chapter 03: "Hunting Cowboy Songs" (2 of 2) (Box-folder 11/399)
    - Chapter 06: "Penitentiary Negroes" (Box-folder 11/400)
    - Chapter 07: "Iron Head and Clear Rock" (Box-folder 11/401)
    - Chapter 09: "Burials, Baptizing and a Penitentiary Sermon" (Box-folder 11/402)
    - Chapter 10: "Chanteys, Ballads, Work Songs and Calls" (Box-folder 11/403)
    - Drafts (1 of 4); primarily notes to the 1940 Southern States recording trip (AFC 1940/003) (Box-folder 12/404)
    - Drafts (2 of 4) (Box-folder 12/405)
    - Drafts (3 of 4) (Box-folder 12/406)
    - Drafts (4 of 4) (Box-folder 12/407)
  - American Folk Song and Folk Lore by Alan Lomax and Sidney Robertson Cowell (1942) forms and correspondence (Box-folder 12/408)
  - Cowboy Songs and Other Frontier Ballads by John A. Lomax (1910) solicitations for contributions, 1907-1909 (Box-folder 12/409)
  - Cowboy Songs and Other Frontier Ballads by John A. Lomax (1938 revised edition)
    - Correspondence and reprint permissions (Box-folder 12/410)
    - Transcripts (Box-folder 12/411)
    - Transcripts including "Doney Gal" (Box-folder 12/412)
    - Proofs of cover and front matter (Box-folder 12/413)
    - Transcripts including "The Cowboy's Ride" (Box-folder 12/414)
    - Galley proofs (Box-folder 16/415)
    - Photostats of melodic transcripts (Box-folder 12/416)
  - Hard Hitting Songs for Hard Hit People by Alan Lomax (1967)
    - Manuscript for publication (Box-folder 13/417)
    - Research notes (1 of 3) (Box-folder 13/418)
    - Research notes (2 of 3) (Box-folder 13/419)
    - Research notes (3 of 3) (Box-folder 13/420)
    - Research notes and song books (1 of 13) (Box-folder 13/421)
    - Research notes and song books (2 of 13) (Box-folder 13/422)
    - Research notes and song books (3 of 13) (Box-folder 13/423)
    - Research notes and song books (4 of 13) (Box-folder 13/424)
    - Research notes and song books (5 of 13) (Box-folder 13/425)
    - Research notes and song books (6 of 13) (Box-folder 13/426)
    - Research notes and song books (7 of 13) (Box-folder 13/427)
    - Research notes and song books (8 of 13) (Box-folder 13/428)
    - Research notes and song books (9 of 13) (Box-folder 13/429)
    - Research notes and song books (10 of 13) (Box-folder 13/430)
    - Research notes and song books (11 of 13) (Box-folder 13/431)
    - Research notes and song books (12 of 13) (Box-folder 13/432)
    - Research notes and song books (11 of 13) (Box-folder 13/433)
  - "List of American Folk Songs on Commercial Records" (1942) manuscript by Alan Lomax (1 of 2) (Box-folder 13/434)
  - "List of American Folk Songs on Commercial Records" (1942) manuscript by Alan Lomax (2 of 2) (Box-folder 13/435)
  - "Listen to Our Story" from "Mr. Jelly Roll" by Alan Lomax (Box-folder 13/436)
  - "Notes on the Songs of Huddie Ledbetter"
    - Contract (Box-folder 13/437)
    - Manuscript for publication (1 of 6) (Box-folder 13/438)
    - Manuscript for publication (2 of 6) (Box-folder 13/439)
    - Manuscript for publication (3 of 6) (Box-folder 14/440)
    - Manuscript for publication (4 of 6) (Box-folder 14/441)
    - Manuscript for publication (5 of 6) (Box-folder 14/442)
    - Manuscript for publication (6 of 6) (Box-folder 14/443)
  - Our Singing Country by John A. Lomax (1941)
    - Correspondence, "Alle en el Rancho Grande" (Box-folder 14/444)
    - Research notes and transcripts (1 of 7) (Box-folder 14/445)
    - Research notes and transcripts (2 of 7) (Box-folder 14/446)
    - Research notes and transcripts (3 of 7) (Box-folder 14/447)
    - Research notes and transcripts (4 of 7) (Box-folder 14/448)
    - Research notes and transcripts (5 of 7) (Box-folder 14/449)
    - Research notes, transcripts, and clippings (6 of 7) (Box-folder 14/450)
    - Research notes and transcripts (6 of 7) (Box-folder 14/451)
Index of Correspondents
Abeel, Ethel M.
Adams, Angela M.
Adamson, Hans Christian
Aldrich, D.G.
Allan-Allan, Baldwin
Allen, James
Allen, Richard
Allen, Robert E.
Alsberg, Henry
Alsberg, Henry G. (Henry Garfield), 1881-1970
Altizer, Mrs. Billy
Anderson, Anna C.
Anderson, Elise E.
Anderson, M. Margaret
Anderson, Thomas W.
Andre, Col.
Andrews, Amelia C.
Andrews, W. B.
Anthony, Charles
Appel, Jean Slater
Archibald, Raymond Clare, 1875-1955
Archuleta, Ricardo
Arizona Highways
Armitage, Harold B.
Arnstein, Joseph
Arthur, B. E.
Ashbey, P.
Augustine, N. R.
Austin, Elizabeth
Babb, W.E.
Babitz, Sol
Baker, James "Iron Head"
Ball, E.C.
Barnicle, Mary Elizabeth, 1891-1978
Bartholomew, Marshall
Basler, Roy P.
Batchelder, Mildred L.
Bayard, E.S.
Bayard, Samuel Preston
Bazer, D.D.
Beachy, Esther Bell
Beachy, Mrs. J.K.
Beck, E.C.
Becker, Arthur
Becker, I.S.
Beckwith, Martha Warren, 1871-1959
Beckworth, Lindley
Bedichek, Roy, 1878-1959
Belden, H. M. (Henry Marvin), 1865-1954
Bell, Arthur
Bell, U.R.
Benedict, Ada S.
Bennett, David P.
Benoit, Cleveland
Benton, Thomas Hart, 1782-1858
Berrien, William
Berry, Charles
Bertram, Anna L.
Bestor, Dorothea N.
Blakely, Robert J.
Blegen, Theodore Christian
Blitzstein, Marc
Boatright, Mody Coggin, 1896-1970
Boddie, William W.
Boehne, John W., Jr.
Boggs, Ralph Steele, 1901-1994
Bond, Horace Mann, 1904-1972
Bond, W.C.
Bonelli, Mary Waller
Boner, C.P.
Bonner, Francis A.
Booram, Priscilla King
Botkin, Benjamin Albert, 1901-1975
Bouck, Harvey J.
Boulton, Laura, 1899-1980
Boyd, Allen R.
Brackett, Carleton R.
Bradford, Thelma
Brandenburg, Margaret J.
Brandon, T.J.
Brandon, W.H., MD
Brandt, Joseph A.
Brassard, Francois-J.
Brecher, Edward M.
Breeden, Lucie E.
Brett, George P.
Brewer, B.T.
Brewster, Paul G.
Bright, J.E.
Brock, J.E.
Brock, Wallace D.
Brockway, Howard
Broome, H.W.
Broome, Harvey
Broussard, James F.
Brown, Charles Edward
Brown, Clara
Brown, Corrine
Brown, Harriet G.
Brown, J.A.
Brown, J.L.
Brown, Joe
Brown, Joe Washington
Brown, Mary Agnes
Brown, Mrs. Cosim
Brown, Sterling Allen, 1901-1989
Bryan, W. J.
Bryant, Dora
Bryson, Lyman
Buchanan, Annabel Morris, 1888-
Buchanan, John P.
Buford A.L.
Bugas, John S.
Bull, David M.
Burchenal, Ruth
Burk, Genevieve S.
Burkhard, Samuel T.
Burns, S.T.
Burton, E. Milby
Butterfield, Roger
Calhoun, J.W.
Campa, Arthur L. (Arthur Leon), 1905-1978
Campbell, Olive D. (Olive Dame), 1882-1954
Caney, Josephine
Cannon, C. L.
Carlisle, Irene Jones
Carneal, Robert B.
Carpenter, Captain Thomas Howard
Carrier, Ogdel
Carty, D.J.
Casey, Smith
Chandler family
Chandler, Elizabeth
Chandler, Genevieve
Chandler, Walter
Chapman, L.F.
Chappell, Lawrence W.
Chappell, Louis V.
Chase, Richard, 1904-1988
Chotas, Denise
Christie, Mabel
Clapp, Verner W. (Verner Warren), 1901-1972
Clark, Evans
Clarke, Eric T.
Claunch, W.E.
Coar, R.J.
Cobb, Ann
Cohen, Henry
Colcord, Joanna C. (Joanna Carver), 1882-1960
Cole, Hilder
Coleman, Merritt H.
Collett, Nonie
Collier, John W.
Collins, Fletcher, Jr., 1906-2005
Colvin, Gertie
Combs, Josiah Henry, 1886-1960
Comhaire-Sylvain, Suzanne
Conroy, Jack
Cooke, Alistair, 1908-2004
Coolidge, Elizabeth Sprague, 1864-1953
Coombs, Josiah
Cornette, Roy
Costello, Elizabeth B.
Cowell, Sidney Robertson, 1903-1995
Cox, John Harrington, 1863-1945
Crane, Edward
Creighton, Helen, 1899-1989
Crim, H.G.
Crisp, John L.
Cross, E.A.
Crozier, Harry Benge
Cubbedge, B.B.
Damon, Arthur H.
Dantzler, L.L.
Darnell, H.C.
Darrow, William H.
Dartigue, M.
Davidson, Julius
Davidson, L.J.
Davis, Hal
Davis, Jackson
Davis, Mary Donald
Davis, Mary Gould
Davis, W.P.
Day, Mrs. Frank
Day, Robert L.
de Onis, Federico
Dealy, Kay
Dennis, Olive W.
Densmore, Frances, 1867-1957
Dick, Sheldon
Dixon, Samuel Clay
Dobie, J. Frank (James Frank), 1888-1964
Dombrowski, James A.
Donovan, Frank, Jr.
Donovan, Richard
Dornbrush, A.J.
Dorr, A.C.
Downes, Olin, 1886-1955
Duggan, Anne Schley
Dunham, Katherine
Dunkle, Colonel
Dyke, Burt
Eaton, Allen
Ebsen, Annette
Eddy, Mary O.
Edgar, Marjorie
Elam, Charles B.
Elliot, Aunt Phoebe
Ellis, Milton
Ellison, Lee
Emrich, Duncan, 1908-1977
Engel, Carl, 1883-1944
Engel, Charles
Erstein, Richard
Evans, Luther Harris, 1902-1981
Evans, M.N.
Evanson, Jacob A. (Jacob Arthur), 1899-1994
Fagel, Edwin
Farr, Irvin F.
Farrar, Nell
Faulk, John Henry
Fenstermaker, Mrs. Charles W.
Fields, Al
Fineschriber, William H.
Finger, Charles Joseph, 1869-1941
Finney, Theodore M.
Fisher, Sterling
Flammer, Harold
Flanders, Helen Hartness, 1890-1972
Flescher, Mary
Ford, A.J.
Ford, Art
Forman, E.C.
Forster Family
Forster, Lilian
Forster, Myrtle
Fort Belvoir Commandant
Foster, E.J.
Foster, Frances M.
Fox, Oscar
Frame, C.H.
Frank, Len
Fray, R.W.
Frazier, Calvin
Frazier, Frank
Frederick A. Stokes Co.
Frederick, John T.
Friedgut, Harry
Friedman, Harold L.
Gamble, Mary Nan
Garde d'Haiti
Garmaize, A.E.
Garwick, Walter C.
Gebeaur, Dorothy
Geer, Will
Gelinas, Paul
Gevedon, J.M.
Gilmore, Marguerite I.
Gladden, Texas, 1895-1966
Goodchild, Donald
Goodwyn, Frank
Gossett, Hon. Ed
Gouger, M.M.
Graham, Mary Nancy
Graves, Mortimer
Green, John W.
Greene, Felix
Greene, Leonard
Griffith, Charles E.
Gross, Lydia
Grover, Carrie B., 1979-1959
Guinan, T.J
Guthrie, Woody, 1912-1967
Hall, Rev. B.D.
Halpert, Herbert, 1911-2000
Hammond, John
Haney, Ova O.
Hanley, Miles L.
Hanna, Paul R.
Hanson, Endicott
Hardiston, Captain
Hardman, W.H.
Harris, Roy
Harris, Sarah
Harwood, Edward
Hawes, Bess Lomax, 1921-2009
Haygood, William C.
Hays, Lee, 1914-1981
Heavener, Mrs. C. Paul
Henderson, Donal
Henry, Sam, 1878-
Hensler, Mrs. George
Hersey, Harold
Herzog, George, 1901-1983
Hickerson, Joseph Charles, 1935-
Hight, T.A.
Hill, George A.
Hill, Mr.
Hill, Richard S.
Hinze, S.W.
Hobden, Ivalee
Hodgson, Hugh
Hogg, Ima
Hoke, George Storer
Holland, E.O.
Holland, Leicester B.
Holmes, Y.W.
Hoover, Gene Boardman
Hopkins, Edith Del
Hopkins, Edith Dell
Hopkins, T.G.
Horton, Lt. Col. Jeter R.
Horton, W.W.
Hough, John, Mrs.
Howard, Mrs. L.S.
Howell, Joseph
Hudson, A.P.
Hudson, Mr.
Hughes, Tom
Hunsaker, Herbert
Hunter, Mabel Neale
Hurston, Zora Neale
Hustvedt, S.B.
Hutchins, William J.
Inman, Elinor F.
Ivens, Joris
Ives, Burl, 1909-1995
Jacobs, Mr.
Jakobson, Svatava
James, Willis, 1900-1966
Jason, Will
Jennings, Edward P.
Johnson, Charles S.
Johnson, Ingrid
Johnson, Paul B.
Jones, Elmer
Jones, John B.
Jones, Mrs. B
Jourtellet, Arthur
Joyce, Doyle
Kahn, Max
Kaldor, Mr. C
Kammerer, Dorothy
Kaplan, Lionel
Kash, Shelby
Kay, Edith W.
Keating, Edward, 1875-1965
Kennard, Margaret
Kennedy, Elsie J.
Kent, Harold W.
Keppel, F.P
Keppel, Frederick P.
Kilgore, Katherine C.
Kimball, Richard H.
King, Gordon
King, J.E.
King, Phillip
King, Stanton H.
King, Willia George
Kirby, David
Kirby, John D.
Kirlkand, Edwin C.
Kittredge, George Lyman, 1860-1941
Kjosness, Valborg
Kleberg, Hon. Richard M.
Korson, George Gershon, 1899-1967
Korson, Rae
Krahl, William F.
Kramer, George Lee
Krimsky, Harold
Krimsky, John
Kromer, Janet
Kubik, Gail
Kwalwasser, Helen
Lach, Chaplain
Lamb, Mrs. Chester E.
Lamothe, L.
Landon, Mrs. H.G.
Landrum, Lynn
Langham, Mrs. E. M.
Larkin, Thomas, III
Latham, E.H.
Lavaud, Frank
Lawson, James R.
Leavitt, Donald L.
Leavitt, Helen S.
Ledbetter, Arthur M.
Ledbetter, Bob
Leadbelly, 1885-1949
Lee, Josephine
Lee, Ronald F.
Leekley, Richard
Leland, Waldo G.
Lengyel, Cornel
Leon, Dr. Rulx
Leslie, John A.
Lester, Robert M.
Levine, Leon
Lewandowski, Stephen
Little, Theo
Lockridge, Ross F.
Lomax, Alan, 1915-2002
Lomax, Alice
Lomax, Bess Brown
Lomax, Elizabeth
Lomax, John A., Jr.
Lomax, John A. (John Avery), 1867-1948
Lomax, Ruby Terrill
Lomax, Shirley
Losey, Joseph
Love, M.P.O.
Loving, Pierre
Luther, Frank
Lutman, George
Lyon, Mary
Lyons, Barrow
Lyons, Clifford P.
MacCutcheon, Robert
MacDonald, Harriet
MacGimsey, Robert, 1898-1979
MacGowan, Clara, 1895-1983
MacKenzie, Robert D.
MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982
Madison, Maury
Magee, Ralph W.
Magistrat communal de Plaisance
Mahon, George Herman, 1900-1985
Maney, Libbie
Manning, Dean
Mansell, Patsy
Mansell, Susan
Marquis, Margaret
Marryat, Sheila
Marsh, Lee
Martinelli, Rose
Massicotte, E.Z.
Mattfeld, Julias
Matthews, Sloan
Maynard, Fred
McCamy, James L.
McCauley, J.E.
McCauley, J.M.
McClane, Effie E.
McDaniel, William R.
McDonald, Martina
McDonald, Montana
McDowell, Mrs. L.L.
McFarland, Frances
McGill, Anna Blanche
McGill, Anne Blanche
McGill, Josephine
McKay, George F.
McLane, Ethel Ferrill
McLauskey, Frances
McNamara, Nell
Mearns, David C.
Megill, Frank
Mellett, Lowell
Mercey, Arch A.
Merrick, L.
Metcalf, Helen M.
Meyer, Elizabeth
Michavitz, Harold
Middleton, C.A.
Miles, Miss
Miles, Myrtle
Mileskay, Veronica
Miller, Olive Beaupré
Miller, Philip L.
Minister of Haiti
Mitchell, James
Mitchell, John
Mitchell, Joseph
Mitchell, Roy
Mlakar, Frank
Moe, Henry Allen
Moody, Dan
Mooney, W.M.
Moore, Arthur K.
Moore, J.A.
Moore, Myrtle
Morgan, George W.
Morgan, Minta
Morrill, J.L.
Morris, Alton Chester
Morris, David
Morris, Jess
Morrison, Dorothy Dunn
Moses, Ted
Moss, E.E.
Muller, Hazel L.
Musick, Ruth Ann
Myers, William A.
Naff, E.D.
Nelson, Alfred C.
Nestler, Harold
Newman, Katharine D., 1911-2001
Newsome, J. D.
Newton, Lesley
Nielson, Alma
Niles, John Jacob, 1892-1980
Nohe, Leo J.
Novik, M.S.
Noyes, Glen H.
Nutt, Mrs. E. Mac
Nye, Pearl R., 1872-1950
Oakdale, Carriere
Oakley, Mrs. Cletus O.
Oathout, Melvin C.
O'Connell, Mr.
Odum, Lonnie
Oliphant, Ronald
Olney, Marguerite
Oursler, Loree H.
Outram, Thomas J.
Owen, W.
Owens, Bess Alice
Paley, William S. (William Samuel), 1901-1990
Palmer, Leo J.
Palmer, Mason
Park, Willard Z. (Willard Zerbe), 1906-1965
Parks, Oscar
Parlin, H.T.
Partch, Harry
Pattison, Janet E.
Paulu, Burton
Payne, A.W.
Pean, Lys
Pedigo, Alice
Penn, R.R.
Perkins, Frances
Perrins, Glen
Peterson, Esther
Petry, Alex
Pfeil, H.H.
Phillips, Howard M.
Pipes, William H.
Pírková-Jakobsonová, Svatava
Pitcher, Gladys
Pitirsau, Esther
Pollard, Lois
Porter, Annie
Posnansky, Arthur
Pound, Louise
Pozman, Gitel
Price, Lt. William H.
Prince, Marie
Prink, Susan S.
Putnam, A.J.
Putnam, George Palmer
Putnam, Herbert, 1861-1955
Putnam, James
Quick, Mrs. Clark
Rael, Juan Bautista
Rainey, Homer P.
Randolph, Vance, 1892-1980
Rautanen, Mrs. Vernon
Ray, Nicholas, 1911-1979
Ray, Thomas James
Rayford, Julian Lee
Rayner, Joan I.
Reben, Alex J.
Reed, Earl C.
Reed, Margaret
Reese, Gustave
Regers, Muriel
Rein, M.L.
Reiser, Mr.
Reynolds, John
Rickard, J. A. (John Allison), 1892-
Ridenour, H.L.
Ritter, Charles G.
Rivers, Rev. G.S.
Roark, Ruth R.
Robbins, Herbert
Roberts, Maurice
Robertson, Ben
Robertson, Lexie Dean
Robin, Harry
Robinson, Ben
Robinson, Earl, 1910-1991
Robinson, Francis Waring
Robinson, Lee Lamar
Rogers, Edgar F.
Rogers, Mary R.
Rollins, Herbert
Rose, Bruce
Rosen, Eugene
Ross, Malcom
Ross, Wilie
Rossell, Beatrice Sawyer
Rossell, J.A.
Rowse, D.G.
Roy, Joseph
Roy, Mrs. Rudolph
Rubic, David
Rutherford, Thomas
Salles, Sarah Buchanan
Sanborn, Marjorie
Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967
Sanders, J. Olcutt